Jun Li



∐ lijun202009@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/junli1220

Profile

A task-oriented and analytical MSc Business Administrator candidate with a specialization in Business Analytics. I am experienced in the HR and Finance fields in the Chinese market. I have developed skillsets using various tools for analysis - Excel, Python, Tableau, Rapid miner, and SQL.

Education

Master

Tias School for Business and Society

08/2021 - 12/2022 | Utrecht, Netherlands

- Major in Business Analytics and elective in Financial Management.
- GPA 7.6 Outstanding at Decision Analysis and Optimization (9.5/10), Business Intelligence (9.0/10), and Business Process and Data Mapping (8.5/10)

Bachelor

Shanghai JiaoQiao College

09/2011 - 06/2016 | ShangHai, China

• Major in Business English



Skills

Python, SQL, Tableau, Excel, Rapidminer, Microsoft offices, IBM chatbot, Flowchart, SPSS



Canguages

English



Chinese

.

Dutch

Professional Experience

Process and Quality Associate IKEA (China) Investment Co., Ltd.,

03/2021 - 08/2021 | ShangHai, China

- Dealt with Accounting Payable issues as a focal point for troubleshooting in the Finance team.
- Dealt with procurement queries regarding orders and payment of internal and external stakeholders and input quantitative data into I-shop and CHS system.
- Working closely with the procurement team, finance team, and store co-workers to make sure all data is accurate.

HR Consultant Specialist Shanghai Talent-spot Group

09/2016 - 05/2018 | ShangHai, China

- Took responsibility for Compensation & Benefits service for 7 international clients on average monthly complying with income tax regulations of China and managed 100+ payroll, social security & housing funds with Excel for individual employees.
- Coordinated onboarding process for internal customers in accordance with recruitment contracts, alien registrations, social security, housing funds, general training, and resignations.
- Assist the software development department in testing the accuracy of HR products.



Projects

IBM Watson Chatbot Designer

05/2022 - 05/2022

• Conversation Engineering - Architect & Entity design, Demonstration



♂ Interests

Outdoor activities, Board games, LGBTQ+ Volunteer



References are available upon request